(Mike M:)It's just, you were scared
and miserable the whole time.
(Bernadette:)I think what we're all trying to say
is, you don't seem to be remembering
(Bernadette:)how traumatic the experience
was for you.
(Raj:)Like how women often forget
the pain of childbirth.
(Mike R:)Like a woman. Great analogy.
(Howard:)Fine, maybe I was a little scared.
(Mike M:)You peed in your space suit.
(Howard:)You're supposed to do that.
(Mike M:)Not during the fitting.
(Mike R:)Son, do I need to remind you
what you asked me to do
(Mike R:)before you went up last time?
(Leonard:)Hang on.
That was just me joking around.
(Mike R:)You wanted me to shoot you
in the foot.
(Howard:)Come on, how is that not a joke?
"You got to get me out of this.
Shoot me in the foot."
(Bernadette:)Don't forget all the other
astronauts picking on you.
(Raj:)And how you threw up
in zero gravity,
(Raj:)and it floated back in your mouth.
(Raj:)And you threw up again.
And so on and so on.
(Mike M:)That was funny.